Ajay has experienced this
Ajay how to
masturbate I welcome you to
Bol Engagement in today's video we will
talk about ICICI Prudential Life Insurance Company because
we are seeing a huge decline in its prices after a few days of profit and
friends on Friday
we saw a decline of about 400 cents in the Play Store
so this can give us an
opportunity to make a good question and
friends before moving forward let me tell you
that we also have a Telegram channel in
which we share the equivalent of a big Paterson option for free
and that too is free of
cost so turn on the channel and
you will find the link in the description below so lt so
friends if we
talk about the company's product then as the
name of the company suggests the company provides life
insurance to its customers
this is their main business and on
Friday we saw a decline of about four percent in this company
which is about 17 paise out of it
75 paise and the current but the
price is Rs. 20 of the stock and the
company's finance will remain  If we talk about it,
you will see the company's revenue in 2019 was Rs
203 crore.
And in 2030, we
saw a huge decline in revenue, which means that the
company's revenue was reduced by half. And
in 2012, you will see a
loss of Rs 203 crore
in the company. If we look at Nottingham in the company, you will see that the
company's net income in 2019 was Rs
108 crore and 2019 is less, there has been a slight
decline and you are getting Nottingham Rs
106 crore. If we
look at the company's balance sheet, you will
see that the company is currently tax free. So, if
we talk about free of cost, then
Africa Shroff means
how much money comes into the company's account at the end of this year,
you will see it in Twenty20. Rs
1102.64 crore. Now we will calculate the
valuation of the company. So,
we will use the pre-earnings ratio here.
You will get the sum of PML-N as
basic 64 and  The sector's price is 31.05. If we
look at Indresh Kumar, we
get an overview of ICICI Prudential Life Insurance Company. This means that if we
check the company's activation, we will see it now.
Now if we organize these by arranging them with pieces, then
friends,
we are getting an appreciation of ICICI Prudential, then
Sikka Edifice Life Insurance will be of 10%
and SBI Life Insurance will be of 10%.
If we compare the two companies, then
we get ICICI Prudential at a very cheap
valuation. Now friends, we
also unravel the chapter. So, friends,
before the stop was presented, we were seen
trading at almost the middle of the light phase.
This market crashed
and on March 24, if we
compare it with 226, then we will see a decline of about 50%. The
office staff appointed 82 recovery officers for
this. And if we talk about the city, then
we saw a decline of about 50%.
Now we will use some indicators, so the
first one is  The indicator I
am using is the Battery Latest
Bank Index, the number we used in the calculator,
Camilla Eight, which is telling us that the
stock is currently in the oversold zone and then it will
see further declines. The
second indicator is the remedy which we can
clearly see that when the red line is
above, it is telling us that
Bairstow is active in the stock and the 13.5 V range, you
can see that the stop, which has to be
placed below its medium flame mark,
means that the kilo and penetrator is being placed.
This tells us that the best friend has just started in the stock
because if you
look at the standard six pattern, the Cancer
6 pattern is also telling us that the establishment question is
active. Now let us talk about support levels. The
first
support level that I would like to give is
only for investors. Friends, what I would like you to
take is the current market
price. If you want, you can
create a press position at the current market price in this topic.
But to make a profit, you should use
it for your long-term investment.  You will have to remain invested
and the second support price that I
would like to give is for application investors
which is ₹400 so friends if you
get a shop in between this level then you
can make Vaishali Express portion so I would just
suggest you that friends do
not lose your courage to invest the entire money in one go, invest it in crime
because of this your always-on investment will become
very good and you will
also get a chance to earn good returns so
those 200 applicants all the decisions are yours
before taking any decision do your complete
study by giving your complete address if you liked the video then
subscribe to the channel like and
set it so we will
meet in the next video till then
hello and you are in the state